I've logged in to my account in Work Auto.
It is a trial account.
I'm going
to use the organization tool projects.
So
I am in projects here
and you can also get it from the left navigation projects.
And
we are going to create a new project here.
So,
I'm gonna click on projects
and use the naming convention,
IT cause that's the department,
and this will be manager.
Computer.
Approval.
Uh,
we're gonna start from scratch and we're going to create
a blank project.
So,
here's our project.
And the first step in our process is we're going to create
the data table,
uh,
the data store,
and that
will represent
the data we're going to send to the
application.
This will contain the resources of
requests made and then eventually have the manager's approval and the who met,
uh,
and the time.
So,
we're gonna create a data table
and we'll give it a name.
And so this is like a database,
so I'll use lowercase,
computer
request
approval.
And I could
order a CSV,
but I'm gonna start from scratch.
And now,
there are some additional columns automatically created for you,
which you can,
we will be using
as a record ID which would be important.
Um,
there's a created time and a last time modified.
So,
we'll go ahead and add the column in here.
The first,
uh,
column
is going to be request your email
and that will be short text.
OK,
and that will be required,
so we'll add that.
Uh the next
column,
which will be device.
Uh,
short text,
uh,
and that will be
what
type,
type of computer?
And
that will be required.
We will have the
cost.
And here,
we can go ahead and change that to decimal.
And then we will have reason,
reason for the request.
So here
we can say that the reasons could be new hire.
Uh,
broken.
Or lost.
I'll make that required.
We'll have the justification.
Why.
Do you need
a laptop?
A computer issued.
Make that required.
We'll add that column.
Status.
Will tell us what's
currently happening,
won't be a field people will fill.
Then we will have
Approver.
Email
And then the last column will be decided at when the decision was made.
And we'll take time.
And at the column.
So now that we have the column,
we can go ahead and we can enter our data in here ourselves.
So
we have new.employeewk@gmail.com will be their email address.
Device,
we will say
Dell.
Yes,
15,
we will say that costs
1899.99.
And we'll say new higher.
Uh,
just
joined the company.
We'll
leave this here and then we'll put.